Prasad G

SAP FICO Consultant at Atos Syntel PVT LTD

8 Year(s) 8 Month(s) | Bangalore/Bengaluru | INR 8.50 Lac(s)

8951015329 gprasadc89@gmail.com

"SAP FICO Consultant seeking roles in SAP FICO, Project Implementation, Project Support, ASAP Methodology, General Ledger, Accounts Receivable, Accounts Payable, Master Data, GI Accounting, Business Process Re-engineering, Integration Testing, Unit Testing

WORK SUMMARY

Having total 8+ years of experience, which includes 4.8 years of experience in SAP FICO module and 4 years in accounting domain. Involved in one End-to-End implementation projects and two support & Maintenance projects. Good expertise on project methodology-ASAP Methodology. SAP FI- General Ledger (FI-GL) Accounts Receivable (FI-AR), Accounts Payable (FI-AP), and Asset Accounting (FI-AA). SAPCO- Cost Element Accounting (CO-CEA), Cost Center Accounting (CO-CCA) and Internal Orders (CO-IO). Good Experience on integration of FI with MM, SD. Experience on validation and substitution. Experience in Configuring and Customizing, data transfers using Batch input methods, transferred master data from legacy system using LSMW. Good Experience on New G/L accounting functionalities. Experience on IDOC process and Monitoring. Manual upload/down load of interface related files, wherever required.

Industry: IT Services & Consulting

Department : Consulting **Role :** Functional Consultant

WORK EXPERIENCE

SAP FICO Consultant Jan 2021 - Till Date

Atos Syntel PVT LTD

Proficient in ASAP Methodology and well versed with business process, its mapping & configuration in SAP. Participated in AS-IS, To-BE Process, business process re-engineering and Business Blueprint Phases in Implementation of SAP. Testing Unit testing, Integration testing & User Acceptance Testing. Strong Exposure on FI Integration with Other modules MM & SD. Participated in Month end and year-end closing processes. Key user training and solving the issues raised by the users

Associate Consultant Apr 2018 - Dec 2020

IBM

* Involved in one End-to-End implementation projects and two support & Maintenance projects. * Good expertise on project methodology-ASAP Methodology. * SAP FI- General Ledger (FI-GL) Accounts Receivable (FI-AR), Accounts Payable (FI-AP), and Asset Accounting (FI-AA). * SAPCO- Cost Element Accounting (CO-CEA), Cost Center Accounting (CO-CCA) and Internal Orders (CO-IO). * Good Experience on integration of FI with MM, SD. * Experience

on validation and substitution. * Experience in Configuring and Customizing, data transfers using Batch input methods, transferred master data from legacy system using LSMW. * Good Experience on New G/L accounting functionalities. * Experience on IDOC process and Monitoring. * Manual upload/down load of interface related files, wherever required. * Excellent communication and inter personnel skills. Proven ability to work independently and team environments. * Experience on finance accountings in Industrial manufacturing sector

Accounts Executive Apr 2014 - Mar 2018

BLUELINER SOFTWARE SERVICES PRIVATE LIMITED

Roles and Responsibilities: Maintaining books of accounts, Bank Reconciliation Statement, Reconciliation statement, TDS deduction, deposit and preparation return. Ensure timely posting of all transactions, preparation of management accounts Implementing systems, procedures & manuals for preparation & maintenance of statutory books of accounts & financial statements. Entire accounting function - Finalization, over viewing Accounts Receivables, Payables, Collections & Bank Reconciliation. Computerization of Accounts of almost all types of business organization using Tally Recording transactions in daily basis in Tally, maintaining books of accounts. All statutory Payments and Filing like TDS, ESI, EPF & Professional Tax

EDUCATION DETAILS

P.G.

MBA/PGDM (Finance) 2012
JNTU College of Engineering, Anantapur

U.G. B.Com (COMPUTERS) 2010

Venkateshwara University

IT SKILLS

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
SAP R3		0	
SAP FICO		0	
SAP HANA	S4	0	
MS OFFICE		0	
Tally ERP	9.0	0	

DESIRED JOB DETAILS

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time
US Work Status: Not Mentioned

Preferred Location : Bangalore/Bengaluru,Hyderabad/Secunderabad,Chennai

PERSONAL DETAILS

Name: Prasad G Gender: Male

Marital Status: Married

Date of Birth: 20 May 1989

Mobile: 8951015329(M)

Email ID: gprasadc89@gmail.com